<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="app_name">SMS Time Fix</string>
	
	<string name="status">Status</string>
	
    <string name="active">Active</string>
    <string name="active_summary_on">
    	Monitor incoming messages
    </string>
    <string name="active_summary_off">
    	Do nothing
    </string>
    
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    
    <string name="offset_method">Offset Method</string>
    <string name="offset_method_summary">Method for adjusting time stamps</string>
    
    <string name="offset">Offset</string>
    <string name="offset_summary">
    	How many hours to adjust incoming messages
    </string>
    
    <string name="cdma">CDMA Option</string>
    <string name="cdma_summary">
    	Only adjust when SMS time is in the future.
    </string>
    
    <string name="set">Set</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
	<string name="help_title">Help</string>
	
	<string name="help_h1">
		Offset Method 
	</string>
	<string name="help_b1">
		This setting determines how the times of incoming messages will be altered. There are three methods available to choose from:
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_h2">
		Automatic
	</string>
	<string name="help_b2">
		This method will dynamically determine how to offset your messages by using your current time zone as the offset value. If you are GMT-5:00 then your messages will be offset by 5 hours.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_h3">
		Manual
	</string>
	<string name="help_b3">
		This method allows you to specify the number of hours to offset incoming messages.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_h4">
		Phone\'s Time
	</string>
	<string name="help_b4">
		This method uses the phone\'s current time as the sent time for all incoming messages. Keep in mind, however, that this method ignores when a message was actually sent, and instead uses when it was received by your phone.
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_h5">
		Offset
	</string>
	<string name="help_b5">
		The offset is the number of hours that you want incoming messages to be shifted by. For example, if a message received at 5:00 PM is being displayed as 1:00PM, then you need to set the offset to <b>4</b> to add four hours to your incoming messages.
		\n<b>NOTE:</b> The offset can be negative!
	</string>
	
	<string name="help_h6">
		CDMA Fix
	</string>
	<string name="help_b6">
		This is a setting for CDMA users with roaming problems. This will only alter the time of an incoming message if the time on the message is in the future.
	</string>
		
	<string name="help_h7">
		I\'m still confused!
		\nIt\'s broken!
		\nThis doesn\'t solve anything!
		\nThis solves everything!
	</string>
	<string name="help_b7">
		I would love to hear from you! Please visit my website http://mattprecious.com to contact me.
	</string>
    
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
	<string name="about_title">About</string>
	
	<string name="about_version">
		Version 2.1
	</string>
	
	<string name="about_by">
		Written by:
	</string>
		
	<string name="about_contact">
		Matthew Precious
		\nhttp://mattprecious.com
	</string>
		
	<string name="about_blurb">
		Please contact me if there are any problems or if you would like to request a new feature. I\'d also love to hear if everything is working! Your feedback is very important to me. Every update I release is due to user feedback.
	</string>
</resources>